'use strict';

const STORE = [
    {
      question: 'What’s the term to describe someone who is either afraid of wine or has an extreme hatred of it?',
      answers: [
        'Ophidiophobia',
        'Oenophobia',
        'Alektorophobia',
        'Wineophobia'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Oenophobia'
    },
    {
      question: 'What famous person in American history is quoted as saying “Wine makes daily life easy, less hurried, with fewer tension and more tolerance."',
      answers: [
        'Benjamin Franklin',
        'Abraham Lincoln',
        'George Washington',
        'Andrew Jackson'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Benjamin Franklin'
    },
    {
      question: 'The term “drinking to one’s health” came from what culture?',
      answers: [
        'The Vikings',
        'Medieval France',
        'Ancient Rome',
        'Ancient Greece'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Ancient Greece'
    },
    {
      question: 'How many varieties of wine grapes exist worldwide?',
      answers: [
        '167',
        '240',
        '5,000',
        '10,000'
        ],
      correctAnswer: '10,000'
    },
    {
      question: 'European wines are named for their geographic location, while non-European wines are named after ...',
      answers: [
        'Whatever a government committee decides',
        'The family that owns the vineyard',
        'The type of grape used to make the wine',
        'Whatever the International Organisation of Vine and Wine decides'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'The type of grape used to make the wine'
    },
    {
      question: 'What’s Eiswein?',
      answers: [
        'A vineyard in California',
        'The oldest type of wine',
        'Wine made from frozen grapes',
        'Wine invented by Albert Einstein'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Wine made from frozen grapes',
    },
    {
      question: 'What country has become the largest consumer of red wine?',
      answers: [
        'China',
        'Italy',
        'France',
        'The United States'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'China',
    },
    {
      question: 'How many bottles of wine can one grapevine produce?',
      answers: [
        '2 bottles',
        '5 bottles',
        '10 bottles',
        'About a bottle and a half'
        ],
      correctAnswer: '10 bottles'
    },
    {
      question: 'How many states have at least one winery?',
      answers: [
        '10 states',
        '12 states',
        '34 states',
        'All 50 states'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'All 50 states',
    },
    {
      question: 'What year was Champagne invented?',
      answers: [
        '1245',
        '1567',
        '1899',
        '1693'
        ],
      correctAnswer: '1693'
    },
];
